I don’t think anyone buys insurance
thinking that they’re going to need it.
And nothing was ever
going to happen to me.
But, it did.
And I was very, very grateful that
we had this particular product.
A few years ago, my husband and I
decided to take on an old house
and renovate it top to bottom
Just two years later,
I was diagnosed with cancer.
My husband and my kids, if they had
to worry about money on top of that,
it just, that would have
been really devastating.
Manulife just took essentially the
biggest bill we have in our life
and took care of it.
Having this product just meant
the world and I think it contributed
to me getting through all
the really tough treatments
that I had to get through.
You never know what’s
going to happen to you.
The better prepared you are,
the better you can face
whatever comes your way.